{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Water Damage Restoration Companies","categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"__cache./api/resource/task/interview/100008/":{"taskOID":100008,"originalTaskOID":100008,"setID":785,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":5666,"questionDisplayText":"Location of Damage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Where is the damage located? (Select all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":3337,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Interior rooms","answerDisplayText":"Interior rooms","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":984,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Bathroom or kitchen","answerDisplayText":"Bathroom or kitchen","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7000,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Window sills/trim","answerDisplayText":"Window sills/trim","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2544,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Flooring","answerDisplayText":"Flooring","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1288,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Ceiling","answerDisplayText":"Ceiling","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6774,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Walls","answerDisplayText":"Walls","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":881,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Attic","answerDisplayText":"Attic","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":969,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Basement or under crawl space","answerDisplayText":"Basement or under crawl space","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2328,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Exterior of house (siding, trim, eaves)","answerDisplayText":"Exterior of house (siding, trim, eaves)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5415,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Roofing","answerDisplayText":"Roofing","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1845,"answerDisplaySequence":11,"answerText":"Deck, porch or other structure","answerDisplayText":"Deck, porch or other structure","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7107,"answerDisplaySequence":12,"answerText":"Wooden fencing or retaining wall","answerDisplayText":"Wooden fencing or retaining wall","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":13,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":5667,"questionDisplayText":"Size of Affected Area","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"How large is the affected area?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5811,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Small area indoors","answerDisplayText":"Small area indoors","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4378,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"One room","answerDisplayText":"One room","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5598,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Several rooms","answerDisplayText":"Several rooms","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5812,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Small area outdoors","answerDisplayText":"Small area outdoors","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3466,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Large area outdoors","answerDisplayText":"Large area outdoors","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":5668,"questionDisplayText":"Signs of Damage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What are the signs of Damage? (Select all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":1738,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Currently damp or wet","answerDisplayText":"Currently damp or wet","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5853,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Soft, rotten or powdery surfaces","answerDisplayText":"Soft, rotten or powdery surfaces","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3905,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Moldy appearance or odor","answerDisplayText":"Moldy appearance or odor","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6906,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Water stains or discoloration","answerDisplayText":"Water stains or discoloration","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1152,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Buckled wood or wallboard","answerDisplayText":"Buckled wood or wallboard","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4632,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Peeling paint","answerDisplayText":"Peeling paint","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2269,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Evidence of insects","answerDisplayText":"Evidence of insects","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":5669,"questionDisplayText":"Noticed Problem","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"How long have you been aware of problem?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":3390,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Just noticed","answerDisplayText":"Just noticed","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1947,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Discovered during inspection","answerDisplayText":"Discovered during inspection","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5597,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Several months","answerDisplayText":"Several months","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3943,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than a year","answerDisplayText":"More than a year","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":1443,"questionDisplayText":"Cause of Damage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Select possible causes of the water damage.","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":6425,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Toilet overflow","answerDisplayText":"Toilet overflow","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4692,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Pipe burst","answerDisplayText":"Pipe burst","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2465,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Fire sprinkler went off","answerDisplayText":"Fire sprinkler went off","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5741,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Sink overflow","answerDisplayText":"Sink overflow","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6836,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Washing machine hose","answerDisplayText":"Washing machine hose","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2069,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Drain back-up","answerDisplayText":"Drain back-up","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5403,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Roof leak","answerDisplayText":"Roof leak","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5808,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Slow or gradual leak or water exposure","answerDisplayText":"Slow or gradual leak or water exposure","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":5670,"questionDisplayText":"Damaged Materials","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What materials are damaged? (Select all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":6771,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Wallboard","answerDisplayText":"Wallboard","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6698,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Vinyl Flooring","answerDisplayText":"Vinyl Flooring","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2928,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Hardwood floor","answerDisplayText":"Hardwood floor","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7094,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Wood sub-floor","answerDisplayText":"Wood sub-floor","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6364,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Tile or grout","answerDisplayText":"Tile or grout","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1218,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Cabinetry or wood trim","answerDisplayText":"Cabinetry or wood trim","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7072,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Wood framing materials","answerDisplayText":"Wood framing materials","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3304,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Insulation","answerDisplayText":"Insulation","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2340,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Exterior wood","answerDisplayText":"Exterior wood","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6159,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Stucco","answerDisplayText":"Stucco","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":11,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":30001,"questionDisplayText":"Historical Work","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this location a historical structure?","shortQuestionText":"Is a historical structure?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":50001,"questionDisplayText":"Covered by Insurance","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this request covered by an insurance claim?","shortQuestionText":"Covered by an insurance claim?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":7,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502713,"questionDisplayText":"Are you interested in financing?","displayToSP":false,"questionDisplaySequence":8,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you interested in financing?","shortQuestionText":"Are you interested in financing?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":5666,"questionDisplayText":"Location of Damage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Where is the damage located? (Select all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":3337,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Interior rooms","answerDisplayText":"Interior rooms","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":984,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Bathroom or kitchen","answerDisplayText":"Bathroom or kitchen","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7000,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Window sills/trim","answerDisplayText":"Window sills/trim","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2544,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Flooring","answerDisplayText":"Flooring","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1288,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Ceiling","answerDisplayText":"Ceiling","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6774,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Walls","answerDisplayText":"Walls","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":881,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Attic","answerDisplayText":"Attic","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":969,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Basement or under crawl space","answerDisplayText":"Basement or under crawl space","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2328,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Exterior of house (siding, trim, eaves)","answerDisplayText":"Exterior of house (siding, trim, eaves)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5415,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Roofing","answerDisplayText":"Roofing","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1845,"answerDisplaySequence":11,"answerText":"Deck, porch or other structure","answerDisplayText":"Deck, porch or other structure","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7107,"answerDisplaySequence":12,"answerText":"Wooden fencing or retaining wall","answerDisplayText":"Wooden fencing or retaining wall","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":13,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":3337,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Interior rooms","answerDisplayText":"Interior rooms","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":984,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Bathroom or kitchen","answerDisplayText":"Bathroom or kitchen","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7000,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Window sills/trim","answerDisplayText":"Window sills/trim","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2544,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Flooring","answerDisplayText":"Flooring","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1288,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Ceiling","answerDisplayText":"Ceiling","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6774,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Walls","answerDisplayText":"Walls","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":881,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Attic","answerDisplayText":"Attic","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":969,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Basement or under crawl space","answerDisplayText":"Basement or under crawl space","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2328,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Exterior of house (siding, trim, eaves)","answerDisplayText":"Exterior of house (siding, trim, eaves)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5415,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Roofing","answerDisplayText":"Roofing","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1845,"answerDisplaySequence":11,"answerText":"Deck, porch or other structure","answerDisplayText":"Deck, porch or other structure","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7107,"answerDisplaySequence":12,"answerText":"Wooden fencing or retaining wall","answerDisplayText":"Wooden fencing or retaining wall","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":13,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":5667,"questionDisplayText":"Size of Affected Area","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"How large is the affected area?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5811,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Small area indoors","answerDisplayText":"Small area indoors","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4378,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"One room","answerDisplayText":"One room","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5598,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Several rooms","answerDisplayText":"Several rooms","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5812,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Small area outdoors","answerDisplayText":"Small area outdoors","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3466,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Large area outdoors","answerDisplayText":"Large area outdoors","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5811,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Small area indoors","answerDisplayText":"Small area indoors","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4378,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"One room","answerDisplayText":"One room","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5598,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Several rooms","answerDisplayText":"Several rooms","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5812,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Small area outdoors","answerDisplayText":"Small area outdoors","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3466,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Large area outdoors","answerDisplayText":"Large area outdoors","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":5668,"questionDisplayText":"Signs of Damage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What are the signs of Damage? (Select all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":1738,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Currently damp or wet","answerDisplayText":"Currently damp or wet","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5853,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Soft, rotten or powdery surfaces","answerDisplayText":"Soft, rotten or powdery surfaces","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3905,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Moldy appearance or odor","answerDisplayText":"Moldy appearance or odor","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6906,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Water stains or discoloration","answerDisplayText":"Water stains or discoloration","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1152,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Buckled wood or wallboard","answerDisplayText":"Buckled wood or wallboard","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4632,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Peeling paint","answerDisplayText":"Peeling paint","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2269,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Evidence of insects","answerDisplayText":"Evidence of insects","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":1738,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Currently damp or wet","answerDisplayText":"Currently damp or wet","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5853,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Soft, rotten or powdery surfaces","answerDisplayText":"Soft, rotten or powdery surfaces","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3905,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Moldy appearance or odor","answerDisplayText":"Moldy appearance or odor","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6906,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Water stains or discoloration","answerDisplayText":"Water stains or discoloration","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1152,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Buckled wood or wallboard","answerDisplayText":"Buckled wood or wallboard","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4632,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Peeling paint","answerDisplayText":"Peeling paint","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2269,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Evidence of insects","answerDisplayText":"Evidence of insects","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":5669,"questionDisplayText":"Noticed Problem","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"How long have you been aware of problem?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":3390,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Just noticed","answerDisplayText":"Just noticed","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1947,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Discovered during inspection","answerDisplayText":"Discovered during inspection","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5597,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Several months","answerDisplayText":"Several months","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3943,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than a year","answerDisplayText":"More than a year","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":3390,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Just noticed","answerDisplayText":"Just noticed","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1947,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Discovered during inspection","answerDisplayText":"Discovered during inspection","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5597,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Several months","answerDisplayText":"Several months","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3943,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than a year","answerDisplayText":"More than a year","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":1443,"questionDisplayText":"Cause of Damage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Select possible causes of the water damage.","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":6425,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Toilet overflow","answerDisplayText":"Toilet overflow","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4692,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Pipe burst","answerDisplayText":"Pipe burst","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2465,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Fire sprinkler went off","answerDisplayText":"Fire sprinkler went off","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5741,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Sink overflow","answerDisplayText":"Sink overflow","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6836,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Washing machine hose","answerDisplayText":"Washing machine hose","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2069,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Drain back-up","answerDisplayText":"Drain back-up","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5403,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Roof leak","answerDisplayText":"Roof leak","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5808,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Slow or gradual leak or water exposure","answerDisplayText":"Slow or gradual leak or water exposure","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":6425,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Toilet overflow","answerDisplayText":"Toilet overflow","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4692,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Pipe burst","answerDisplayText":"Pipe burst","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2465,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Fire sprinkler went off","answerDisplayText":"Fire sprinkler went off","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5741,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Sink overflow","answerDisplayText":"Sink overflow","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6836,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Washing machine hose","answerDisplayText":"Washing machine hose","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2069,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Drain back-up","answerDisplayText":"Drain back-up","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5403,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Roof leak","answerDisplayText":"Roof leak","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5808,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Slow or gradual leak or water exposure","answerDisplayText":"Slow or gradual leak or water exposure","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":5670,"questionDisplayText":"Damaged Materials","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What materials are damaged? (Select all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":6771,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Wallboard","answerDisplayText":"Wallboard","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6698,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Vinyl Flooring","answerDisplayText":"Vinyl Flooring","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2928,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Hardwood floor","answerDisplayText":"Hardwood floor","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7094,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Wood sub-floor","answerDisplayText":"Wood sub-floor","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6364,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Tile or grout","answerDisplayText":"Tile or grout","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1218,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Cabinetry or wood trim","answerDisplayText":"Cabinetry or wood trim","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7072,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Wood framing materials","answerDisplayText":"Wood framing materials","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3304,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Insulation","answerDisplayText":"Insulation","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2340,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Exterior wood","answerDisplayText":"Exterior wood","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6159,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Stucco","answerDisplayText":"Stucco","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":11,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":6771,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Wallboard","answerDisplayText":"Wallboard","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6698,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Vinyl Flooring","answerDisplayText":"Vinyl Flooring","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2928,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Hardwood floor","answerDisplayText":"Hardwood floor","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7094,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Wood sub-floor","answerDisplayText":"Wood sub-floor","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6364,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Tile or grout","answerDisplayText":"Tile or grout","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1218,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Cabinetry or wood trim","answerDisplayText":"Cabinetry or wood trim","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7072,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Wood framing materials","answerDisplayText":"Wood framing materials","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3304,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Insulation","answerDisplayText":"Insulation","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2340,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Exterior wood","answerDisplayText":"Exterior wood","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6159,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Stucco","answerDisplayText":"Stucco","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":11,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":30001,"questionDisplayText":"Historical Work","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this location a historical structure?","shortQuestionText":"Is a historical structure?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":50001,"questionDisplayText":"Covered by Insurance","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this request covered by an insurance claim?","shortQuestionText":"Covered by an insurance claim?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":7,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502713,"questionDisplayText":"Are you interested in financing?","displayToSP":false,"questionDisplaySequence":8,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you interested in financing?","shortQuestionText":"Are you interested in financing?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]},"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"isMobile":false,"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","semThreeIcons":false,"isCookielessUser":true,"__cache./api/resource/task/100008/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":100008,"taskName":"Dry-rot, Water or Pest Damage - Major Repair","taskDescription":"Repair Damage from Dry-rot, Water or Pests","xmTaskDescriptor":"Water Damage Restoration Companies","matchable":false,"profileable":true,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":305,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"Dry-rot Major rot recovery dryrot","textMessagingName":"Damage Recovery","rolloverLongDesc":"Repair or replace wood, wallboard or building materials which deteriorate or rot due to long-term exposure to water, mold \u0026 mildew \u0026/or pests such as termites or carpenter ants.","rolloverShortDesc":"For wood, wallboard or other building materials.","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Repair Damage from Dry-rot, Water or Pests.  HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated contractors in your area","htmlTitle":"Water Damage Restoration \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Dry-Rot Damage Repair","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":63,"acceptGoal":4,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":0,"bridgeTaskOid":0,"bridgeTaskText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkId":0,"bridgeTaskActive":"N","xmName":"Dry-rot, Water or Pest Damage Repair","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Dry-rot, Water or Pest Damage - Major Repair","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Major Damage Repair Project","urlName":"Dry-rot-Water-or-Pest-Damage-Major-Repair","taskConsiderationId":2,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":false,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Water Damage Restoration Services - \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | HomeAdvisor Dry-Rot Damage Repair","searchKeywords":"Dry-rot,Major,rot,recovery,dryrot,dry,Damage,Water,Pest","emcCategoryOid":-12022,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":785,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false}}